DETAILS

Eastern Province - Dammam Al-Rakah - King Faisal Road Dammam, P.O.BOX 7772, Khobar Saudi Arabia +966 59 141 0950 Khaldalsaif@gmail.com

> Date / Place of birth 2000/10/18

Dammam

Nationality Saudi

LINKS

<u>GitHub</u>

**YouTube** 

<u>LinkedIn</u>

SKILLS

**Pentesting** 

**Incident Response** 

Programing (Python, Java, c++)

Database (MySQL)

Web (JS, HTML, CSS, PHP)

Web Security

LANGUAGES

ع | Arabic

English | Æ

• PERSONAL SKILLS •

Teamwork

Creativity

Fast Learning

Speaking Skills

# KHALID SAIF AL-SAIF

**UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT** 

#### PROFILE

I am a dedicated and goal-oriented guy with a strong interest in the Cybersecurity and IOT filed.

I am adaptable, dependable, and have outstanding time management abilities. I am a person who is energetic, self-motivated, trustworthy, responsible, and hardworking.

I am an experienced team player that can adjust to any scenario.

I can operate well in a team setting as well as on my own initiative.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

member of media committee ccist at CCIST Club,

Dammam - July 2021 — Present

Registration support at Imam Abdulrahman bin Faisal University -

June 2020 — August 2020

- -Admission and Registration Committee of the University full time
- -Supporting in registration issues & arrange the applicant papers and guide them to the right process

customer service representative at professional technology solutions for communication & technology, Khobar

February 2019 — May 2021

- -sales and customer services for IT solution shop
- dealing with software installation and hardware compatibility
- -provide network solutions for home and small institutions

### **EDUCATION**

BS, Imam Abdulrhaman bin Faisal University, Dammam

September 2018 — June 2023

### REFERENCES

Dr.Abdullah Al-Muhaideb from IAU

amalmuhaideb@iau.edu.sa · +966 55 588 8810

Mr.Ali Al-Zahrani from professional technology solutions

Ali.alzahrani@protec-sa.com · +966 54 628 8844

### **ACHIEVEMENT**

certificate of completion (eJPT)

February 2022

eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester Certification

Completing Cybercraft program Solution by STC, Khobar

July 2018 — August 2018

Certification of Appreciation, Dammam from IAU

for Exploring a critical personal information exposure in Student Information System